Register of the William H. Rehnquist papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Invitations, 1971-2005
  - Declined, 1971-2005
    Consists of invitations, correspondence and notes regarding events that Rehnquist declined to attend. From 1971-1979, the files reflect invitations to speak or judge moot court competitions. After 1980, the files also include social events. Arranged chronologically by date that the invitation was received. Beginning in October 1986 the invitations are separated by the October Term year (The Supreme Court term begins on the first Monday of October, so a letter dated in September 1987 would be filed with the 1986 October term), and are further subdivided alphabetically by the name of the person or institution extending the invitation. Significant gaps exist in October Terms 1989 and 1991. The entirety of Rehnquist's first year on the court, 1972, has been retained, along with the year he was nominated chief justice, 1986, and his last year on the court, 2004. For the years 1974-1985 and 1987-2003 a random representative sample of one fifth of the original materials are retained.
    - 1971 November (Box-folder 294: 4)
    - 1971 December - 1972 January (Box-folder 294: 5)
    - 1972 February (Box-folder 294: 6)
    - 1972 March (Box-folder 294: 7)
    - 1972 April-June (Box-folder 294: 8)
    - 1972 July-October (Box-folder 294: 9)
    - 1972 November - 1973 January (Box-folder 294: 10)
    - 1973 February-May (Box-folder 294: 11)
    - 1973 July (Box-folder 295: 1)
    - 1973 August-December (Box-folder 295: 2)
    - 1974 January-December (Box-folder 295: 3)
    - 1975 January-December (Box-folder 295: 4)
    - 1976 January-December (Box-folder 295: 5)
    - 1977 January-December (Box-folder 295: 6)
    - 1978 January-December (Box-folder 295: 7)
    - 1979 January-December (Box-folder 295: 8)
    - 1980 January-December (Box-folder 295: 9)
    - 1983 January-December (Box-folder 295: 10)
    - 1984 June-December (Box-folder 295: 11)
    - 1985 January-August (Box-folder 295: 12)
    - 1985 September-December (Box-folder 295: 13)
    - 1986 January (Box-folder 296: 1)
    - 1986 February (Box-folder 296: 2)
    - 1986 March (Box-folder 296: 3)
    - 1986 April (Box-folder 296: 4)
    - 1986 May (Box-folder 296: 5)
    - 1986 June (Box-folder 296: 6)
    - 1986 October Term A, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 297: 1-3)
    - 1986 October Term B, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 297: 4)
    - 1986 October Term C, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 297: 5-6)
    - 1986 October Term D-E, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 297: 7)
    - 1986 October Term F, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 297: 8)
    - 1986 October Term G, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 298: 1)
    - 1986 October Term H, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 298: 2)
    - 1986 October Term I-J, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 298: 3)
    - 1986 October Term L-K, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 298: 4)
    - 1986 October Term M, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 298: 5)
    - 1986 October Term N, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 298: 6-8)
    - 1986 October Term O-Q, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 299: 1)
    - 1986 October Term R, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 299: 2)
    - 1986 October Term S, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 299: 3-5)
    - 1986 October Term T-V, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 299: 6)
    - 1986 October Term W-Z, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 299: 7)
    - Speeches 1986 October Term A, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 300: 1-3)
    - Speeches 1986 October Term B, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 300: 4-5)
    - Speeches 1986 October Term C, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 300: 6-8)
    - Speeches 1986 October Term D-E, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 300: 9)
    - Speeches 1986 October Term F-G, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 301: 1)
    - Speeches 1986 October Term H, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 301: 2)
    - Speeches 1986 October Term I-K, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 301: 3)
    - Speeches 1986 October Term L, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 301: 4)
    - Speeches 1986 October Term M, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 301: 5)
    - Speeches 1986 October Term N, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 301: 6-7)
    - Speeches 1986 October Term O, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 301: 8)
    - Speeches 1986 October Term P, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 302: 1-2)
    - Speeches 1986 October Term R-S, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 302: 3)
    - Speeches 1986 October Term T, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 302: 4)
    - Speeches 1986 October Term U-V, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 302: 5-6)
    - Speeches 1986 October Term W-Z, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 302: 7)
    - 1986 October Term A-Z, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 302: 8-9)
    - Speeches 1987 October Term A, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 302: 10)
    - Speeches 1987 October Term A-E, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 303: 1)
    - Speeches 1987 October Term F-M, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 303: 2)
    - Speeches 1987 October Term A-M, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 303: 3)
    - Speeches 1987 October Term N-Z, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 303: 4)
    - October 1987 Term A-Z, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 303: 5)
    - Speeches 1988 October Term A-E, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 303: 6)
    - Speeches 1988 October Term F-M, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 303: 7-8)
    - October 1988 Term M-N, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 303: 9)
    - October 1988 Term N-Q, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 303: 10)
    - Speeches 1988 October Term O-S, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 304: 1)
    - 1988 October Term S, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 304: 2)
    - 1988 October Term R-T, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 304: 3)
    - Speeches 1988 October Term T-Z, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 304: 4)
    - Speeches 1988 October Term N-Z, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 304: 5)
    - 1988 October Term W-Z, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 304: 6)
    - 1989 October Term A-M, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 304: 7)
    - 1989 October Term S, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 304: 8-9)
    - 1989 October Term N-Z, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 305: 1-2)
    - 1990 October Term A, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 305: 3)
    - 1990 October Term B, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 305: 4)
    - 1990 October Term C-E, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 305: 5)
    - 1990 October Term F-J, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 305: 6)
    - 1990 October Term K-M, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 305: 7)
    - 1990 October Term M, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 305: 8)
    - 1990 October Term N-Q, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 305: 9)
    - 1990 October Term R-S, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 305: 10)
    - 1990 October Term T-Z, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 305: 11)
    - Speeches 1990 October Term A-Z, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 305: 12)
    - 1991 October Term A-Z, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 305: 13)
    - 1992 October Term A, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 306: 1)
    - 1992 October Term B-C, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 306: 2)
    - 1992 October Term D-H, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 306: 3)
    - 1992 October Term I-M, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 306: 4)
    - 1992 October Term N-R, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 306: 5)
    - 1992 October Term S-T, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 306: 6)
    - 1992 October Term U-Z, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 306: 7)
    - 1993 October Term A, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 306: 8)
    - 1993 October Term B, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 306: 9)
    - 1993 October Term C-D, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 307: 1)
    - 1993 October Term E-H, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 307: 2)
    - 1993 October Term I-K, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 307: 3)
    - 1993 October Term M-N, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 307: 4)
    - 1993 October Term N-R, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 307: 5)
    - 1993 October Term S-T, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 307: 6)
    - 1993 October Term U-Z, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 307: 7)
    - 1994 October Term A, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 307: 8-9)
    - 1994 October Term B, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 307: 10)
    - 1994 October Term C, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 307: 11)
    - 1994 October Term D-F, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 308: 1)
    - 1994 October Term G-J, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 308: 2)
    - 1994 October Term K-M, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 308: 3)
    - 1994 October Term N-O, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 308: 4)
    - 1994 October Term P-R, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 308: 5)
    - 1994 October Term S, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 308: 6)
    - 1994 October Term S-V, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 308: 7)
    - 1994 October Term W-Z, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 308: 8)
    - 1995 October Term A, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 308: 9)
    - 1995 October Term A-B, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 308: 10)
    - 1995 October Term C, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 308: 11)
    - 1995 October Term D-F, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 309: 1)
    - 1995 October Term G-H, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 309: 2)
    - 1995 October Term I-K, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 309: 3)
    - 1995 October Term L-M, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 309: 4)
    - 1995 October Term N, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 309: 5)
    - 1995 October Term O-R, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 309: 6)
    - 1995 October Term S, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 309: 7)
    - 1995 October Term T-Z, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 309: 8)
    - 1996 October Term A-F, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 309: 9)
    - 1996 October Term G-M, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 309: 10)
    - 1996 October Term N-O, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 309: 11)
    - 1996 October Term P-S, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 310: 1)
    - 1996 October Term T-Z, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 310: 2)
    - 1997 October Term A, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 310: 3)
    - 1997 October Term B, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 310: 4)
    - 1997 October Term C-D, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 310: 5)
    - 1997 October Term E-G, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 310: 6)
    - 1997 October Term H, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 310: 7)
    - 1997 October Term I-J, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 310: 8)
    - 1997 October Term K-L, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 310: 9)
    - 1997 October Term M, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 310: 10)
    - 1997 October Term N, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 310: 11)
    - 1997 October Term N-O, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 310: 12)
    - 1997 October Term P-R, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 311: 1)
    - 1997 October Term S, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 311: 2-3)
    - 1997 October Term T-V, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 311: 4)
    - 1997 October Term W-Z, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 311: 5)
    - 1998 October Term A, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 311: 6)
    - 1998 October Term B-C, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 311: 7)
    - 1998 October Term C-D, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 311: 8)
    - 1998 October Term E-G, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 311: 9)
    - 1998 October Term H-J, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 311: 10)
    - 1998 October Term K-L, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 311: 11)
    - 1998 October Term M, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 311: 12)
    - 1998 October Term N, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 312: 1-2)
    - 1998 October Term O-R, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 312: 3)
    - 1998 October Term S, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 312: 4)
    - 1998 October Term S-T, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 312: 5)
    - 1998 October Term U-Z, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 312: 6)
    - 1999 October Term A, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 312: 7-8)
    - 1999 October Term B, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 312: 9)
    - 1999 October Term C, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 312: 10)
    - 1999 October Term D-F, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 312: 11)
    - 1999 October Term G, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 312: 12)
    - 1999 October Term H, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 313: 1)
    - 1999 October Term I-L, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 313: 2)
    - 1999 October Term M, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 313: 3)
    - 1999 October Term N, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 313: 4-5)
    - 1999 October Term N-O, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 313: 6)
    - 1999 October Term P-R, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 313: 7)
    - 1999 October Term S, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 313: 8-9)
    - 1999 October Term T-V, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 313: 10)
    - 1999 October Term W-Z, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 313: 11)
    - 2000 October Term A, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 313: 12)
    - 2000 October Term A-B, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 314: 1)
    - 2000 October Term C, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 314: 2)
    - 2000 October Term D-F, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 314: 3)
    - 2000 October Term G-H, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 314: 4)
    - 2000 October Term I-K, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 314: 5)
    - 2000 October Term L-M, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 314: 6)
    - 2000 October Term N-O, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 314: 7)
    - 2000 October Term P-R, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 314: 8)
    - 2000 October Term S, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 314: 9)
    - 2000 October Term T-V, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 314: 10)
    - 2000 October Term W-Z, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 314: 11)
    - 2001 October Term A, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 315: 1)
    - 2001 October Term B-C, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 315: 2)
    - 2001 October Term C-D, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 315: 3)
    - 2001 October Term E-F, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 315: 4)
    - 2001 October Term G-H, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 315: 5)
    - 2001 October Term I-J, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 315: 6)
    - 2001 October Term K-L, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 315: 7)
    - 2001 October Term M-N, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 315: 8)
    - 2001 October Term N-O, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 315: 9)
    - 2001 October Term P-R, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 316: 1)
    - 2001 October Term S, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 316: 2)
    - 2001 October Term S-T, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 316: 3)
    - 2001 October Term U-Z, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 316: 4)
    - 2002 October Term A-B, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 316: 5)
    - 2002 October Term C, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 316: 6)
    - 2002 October Term D-G, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 316: 7)
    - 2002 October Term H-K, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 316: 8)
    - 2002 October Term L-M, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 316: 9)
    - 2002 October Term N, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 317: 1)
    - 2002 October Term O-R, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 317: 2)
    - 2002 October Term S-T, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 317: 3)
    - 2002 October Term U-Z, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 317: 4)
    - 2003 October Term A-B, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 317: 5)
    - 2003 October Term C-D, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 317: 6)
    - 2003 October Term E-G, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 317: 7)
    - 2003 October Term H-K, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 317: 8)
    - 2003 October Term L-M, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 317: 9)
    - 2003 October Term N-R, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 318: 1)
    - 2003 October Term S-T, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 318: 2)
    - 2003 October Term U-W, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 318: 3)
    - 2004 October Term A, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 318: 4-7)
    - 2004 October Term B, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 318: 8-9)
    - 2004 October Term C, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 319: 1-3)
    - 2004 October Term D-E, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 319: 4)
    - 2004 October Term F, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 319: 5-6)
    - 2004 October Term G, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 319: 7)
    - 2004 October Term H, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 319: 8)
    - 2004 October Term I-J, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 319: 9)
    - 2004 October Term K, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 320: 1)
    - 2004 October Term L, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 320: 2)
    - 2004 October Term M, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 320: 3)
    - 2004 October Term N, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 320: 4-7)
    - 2004 October Term O-Q, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 320: 8)
    - 2004 October Term R, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 321: 1)
    - 2004 October Term S, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 321: 2-4)
    - 2004 October Term T, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 321: 5)
    - 2004 October Term U-V, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 321: 6)
    - 2004 October Term W, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 321: 7-8)
- CLOSED - Impeachment Files, 1998-2000 (Boxes 322-331, 893)
  Access
  CLOSED during the lifetime of any member of the Supreme Court who served with William H. Rehnquist.
- Notebooks and Calendars, 1969-2005
  The notebooks contain a daily schedule including meetings, appointments, reminders, and notes from 1969-1980. Large monthly calendars include appointments and notes dating from 1973-2004, while smaller desk calendars contain daily notes from 1970-2005.
  - Notebooks, 1969-1980
    - 1-11, 1969 (Box 332)
    - 12-22, 1970 (Box 332)
    - 23-24, 1970 (Box 332)
    - 25-36, 1971 (Box 333)
    - 37-40, 1972 (Box 333)
    - 41-44, 1973 (Box 333)
    - 45-52, 1974 (Box 334)
    - 53-60, 1975 (Box 334)
    - 61 and unnumbered, 1976 (Box 334)
    - 1977 (Box 334)
    - 1978 (Box 335)
    - 1979 (Box 335)
    - 1980 (Box 335)
    - undated (3 notebooks) (Box 335)
  - Daily reminder notebooks
    - 1970 (Box 335)
    - 1971 (Box 335)
    - 1972 (Box 335)
    - 1973 (Box 336)
    - 1974 (Box 336)
    - 1975 (Box 336)
    - 1976 (Box 336)
    - 1977 (Box 336)
    - 1978 (Box 336)
    - 1979 (Box 336)
    - 1980 (Box 336)
  - Monthly appointment calendars
    - 1973 (Box 337)
    - 1974 (Box 337)
    - 1975 (Box 337)
    - 1976 (Box 337)
    - 1977 (Box 337)
    - 1978 (Box 337)
    - 1979 (Box 337)
    - 1980 (Box 337)
    - 1981 (Box 337)
    - 1982-1984 (Box 337)
    - 1991 (Box 337)
    - 1993 (Box 337)
    - 1994 (Box 337)
    - 1995 (Box 337)
    - 1996 (Box 337)
    - 1997 (Box 337)
    - 1998 (Box 337)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 337)
    - 2000 (Box 337)
    - 2001 (Box 337)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 337)
    - 2002 (Box 337)
    - 2003 (Box 337)
    - 2004 (Box 337)
  - Daily calendars
    - 1970 (Box 338)
    - 1971 (Box 338)
    - 1972 (Box 338)
    - 1973 (Box 338)
    - 1974 (Box 338)
    - 1975 (Box 338)
    - 1976 (Box 339)
    - 1977 (Box 339)
    - 1978 (Box 339)
    - 1979 (Box 339)
    - 1980 (Box 339)
    - 1982 (Box 339)
    - 1995 (Box 340)
    - 1996 (Box 340)
    - 1997 (Box 340)
    - 1998 (Box 340)
    - 1999 (Box 340)
    - 2000 (Box 340)
    - 2001 (Box 341)
    - 2002 (Box 341)
    - 2003 (Box 341)
    - 2004 (Box 341)
    - 2005 (Box 341)
- Event Files, 1971-2005
  Consists of invitations, scripts, correspondence, oath cards, maps, and transcripts relating to official events in which the Chief Justice participated. Includes files documenting Rehnquist's own confirmation hearings, funerals and memorial services, presidential inaugurations, and Supreme Court investitures. Arranged by type of event, then chronologically.
  - Confirmation Hearings, 1971 (Box-folder 342: 1-8)
  - Memorial Service for Justice Stewart, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 343: 1-2)
  - Funeral of Mrs Earl Warren, 1993 (Box-folder 343: 3)
  - Funeral of Justice Marshall, 1993 (Box-folder 343: 4)
  - Funeral of President Nixon, 1994 (Box-folder 343: 5)
  - Funeral of Mrs Burger, 1994 (Box-folder 343: 6)
  - Funeral of Chief Justice Burger, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 343: 7-9)
  - Funeral of Mrs Powell, 1996 (Box-folder 343: 10)
  - Funeral of Justice Brennan, 1997 (Box-folder 343: 11)
  - Memorial for Justice Brennan, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 344: 1)
  - Funeral of Justice Powell, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 344: 2)
  - Memorial for Justice Powell, 1999 (Box-folder 344: 3)
  - Funeral of Justice Blackmun, 1999 (Box-folder 344: 4)
  - Memorial for Justice Blackmun, 1999 (Box-folder 344: 5)
  - Funeral of Justice White, 2002 (Box-folder 344: 6)
  - Memorial for Justice White, 2002 (Box-folder 344: 7)
  - Funeral of President Reagan, 2004 (Box-folder 344: 8-9)
  - Presidential Proclamation on Death of President Reagan, 2004 (Box-folder 356)
  - Inauguration of George H W Bush, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 344: 10)
  - Inauguration of George H W Bush, 1988-1989 Includes photographs (Box-folder 345: 1-3)
  - Inauguration of William Clinton, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 345: 4-5)
  - Inauguration of William Clinton, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 345: 6)
  - Inauguration of George W Bush, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 345: 8-9)
  - Inauguration of George W Bush, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 345: 10)
  - Inauguration of George W Bush, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 346: 1)
  - Investiture of Anthony Kennedy, 1988 (Box-folder 346: 2)
  - Investiture of David Souter, 1990 (Box-folder 346: 3)
  - Investiture of Clarence Thomas, 1991 (Box-folder 346: 4-5)
  - Investiture of Ruth Bader Ginsberg, 1993 (Box-folder 346: 6-7)
  - Investiture of Stephen Breyer, 1994 (Box-folder 346: 8-9)
- Federal Judiciary Administrative Files, 1974-1996
  Contains correspondence and reports relating to the administration of the federal court system. Includes material on the Administrative Office of the U. S. Courts and documents the interactions between Rehnquist and the Federal Judicial Conference. Arranged in chronological order.
  - Judiciary Breakfast Group, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 347: 1)
  - Commission on the Appellate System, 1975 (Box-folder 347: 2-3)
  - Rules of Criminal Procedure Amendments, 1981 (Box-folder 347: 4)
  - Federal Judicial Conference Board Meetings, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 347: 5)
  - Federal Judicial Conference, 1991 (Box-folder 347: 6-8)
  - Federal Judicial Conference, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 347: 9)
  - Federal Judicial Conference, 1992 (Box-folder 347: 10-11)
  - Federal Judicial Conference, 1992 (Box-folder 348: 1-5)
  - Judges Taking Senior Status, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 348: 6)
  - Judges Taking Senior Status, 1994 (Box-folder 348: 7)
  - Judges Taking Senior Status, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 348: 8)
  - Judges Taking Senior Status, 1996 (Box-folder 348: 9)
  - Federal Judicial Center Correspondence, 1994 (Box-folder 349: 1-2)
  - Judges' Correspondence, 1995 (Box-folder 349: 3-5)
  - Administrative Office Correspondence, 1995 (Box-folder 349: 6-9)
  - Administrative Office Correspondence, 1995 (Box-folder 350: 1)
- National Historic and Public Records Commission Files, 1982-1986
  Consists of correspondence, agendas, minutes, reports, and members briefing book relating to Rehnquist's service on the National Historic and Public Records Commission representing the Supreme Court. Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - Agenda and minutes, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 350: 2)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box-folder 350: 3)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 350: 4-5)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 350: 6-8)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box-folder 350: 9)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 350: 10)
  - Members Briefing Book, 1983 (Box-folder 351: 1)
  - Reports, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 351: 2)
  - Reports, 1983 (Box-folder 351: 3)
- Supreme Court of the United States, Employee Photograph Directories, 1991-2003
  Printed identification, phone, and location directories for Supreme Court employees.
  - 1991-1992 Term (Box 352)
  - 1993-1994 October Terms (Box 352)
  - 1996-2004 October Terms (Box 352)
- Personal Files and Miscellany, 1969-2005
  Includes articles, biographical and genealogical data, correspondence, notes, and audiovisual material documenting Rehnquist's hobbies and interests outside of the court. Also documents published perceptions of Rehnquist's life and career. Arranged alphabetically by folder title; audiovisual material filed separately in chronological order.
  - Articles, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 353: 1)
  - Articles, 1985-1991 (Box 356)
  - Articles, 2005 (Box-folder 353: 2-3)
  - Biographical Data, 1969-1980 (Box-folder 353: 4)
  - Correspondence for Natalie Rehnquist, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 353: 5)
  - Genealogy, 1971-2003 (Box-folder 353: 6)
  - Genealogy, 1988 Includes photographs (Box-folder 353: 7)
  - Genealogy, 1989 (Box-folder 353: 8)
  - George Washington University Honorary Degree, 1996 (Box 356)
  - Hobbies, 1970-2005 (Box-folder 353: 9)
  - Interview of Chief Justice Rehnquist by David Rubinstine, audiocassette, 1989 January 4 (Box 355)
  - Interviews, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 353: 10)
  - Items on Desk - Front Office, 2004 (Box-folder 353: 11)
  - Items on Desk - Front Office, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 353: 12)
  - Items on Desk - Back Office, 1987-2002 (Box-folder 354: 1)
  - Items on Desk - Back Office, 1992-2004 (Box-folder 354: 2)
  - Portrait of Justice Robert Jackson, 2003 (Box 356)
  - Speeches of others, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 356: 3-4)
  - The Phoenix 2: A Tribute to Frank Snell and Mark Wilmer, videotape, 1988 (Box-folder 355: 1)
  - The Trial of Richard III, videotape, 1996 (Box-folder 355: 2)
  - Ronald Reagan and Pope John Paul II: Faith, Freedom, and the Collapse of Communism, compact disc, 2001 (Box-folder 355: 3)
  - National Air and Space Museum dedication medal, 2003 (Box-folder 355: 4)
  - Grand Canyon University Graduation, compact disc, 2005 (Box-folder 355: 5)
  - Paintings by Mona Rehnquist, compact disc, undated (Box-folder 355: 6)
  - Russian Constitutional Court medal, undated (Box-folder 355: 7)
- CLOSED - U.S. Supreme Court Case Files and Related Materials, 1975-2005 (Boxes 359-892)
  Conditions Governing Access note